

Bogoslavskyi Igor
Nationality:
Ukrainian
Family:
single
no children

**Phone:** +49 (0152) 04471543 **Address:** 

Händelstrasse 20, 79104, Freiburg im Br. Germany

On the Net: igor.bogoslavskyi@gmail.com

LinkedIn::Igor Bogoslavskyi

GitHub::niosus

Facebook::bogoslavskyi

G+::Igor Bogoslavskyi

# Igor Bogoslavskyi

## **Computer Science Student**

#### About me

I am a young computer science specialist, particularly interested in Robotics, Machine Learning and Computer Vision fields of study.

I am fond of the idea of autonomous moving vehicles and look forward to having a chance of facing the problems that arise in this field.

The best way to contact me would be just to send an e-mail.

## **Experience**

#### January 2012 - present, Assistant in AIS lab Albert Ludwigs University of Freiburg, Germany

 As an assistant in the Autonomous Intelligent Systems lab at Uni Freiburg, I dealt with Kinect RGBD sensors mounted onto various platforms as well as unmounted, with relation to RGBD object segmentation and traversability analysis.

#### June 2012 - April 2013, Assistant in HRL lab Albert Ludwigs University of Freiburg, Germany

 As an assistant in the Humanoid Robots Lab at Uni Freiburg, I dealt with Kinect RGBD sensors mounted onto the NAO robot platform with relation to gesture analysis.

## November 2011 - April 2012, Tutor in Image Processing class

#### Albert Ludwigs University of Freiburg, Germany

- As a tutor in the chair of Computer Vision and Image Processing at Uni Freiburg my tasks were to help my fellow students to accomplish the course programming assignments.
- Involved c++ programming with relation to blurring/deblurring, optical flow and segmentation tasks.

# December 2010 - October 2011, Junior Software Developer Timecode LLC, Kyiv, Ukraine

- worked as part of a team on a game for Android platform.
   Involved Java Android programming, OpenGL.
- worked as part of a team on an Online Content Store controlled via Kinect sensor. Mostly finding and fixing bugs. C#.

## **Education**

2011 - present, Albert-Ludwigs-Universitt Freiburg

MSc. Applied Computer Science

2007 - 2011, Kyiv National Taras Shevchenko University

BSc. Faculty of Cybernetics. Applied Math field.

Chair of Computational Methods

2004 - 2007, Lyceum 145, Kyiv

Higher basic education certificate, Mathematics, Physics.

## **Projects**

#### from October 2012, ROVINA Project

- ROVINA Robots for Exploration, Digital Preservation and Visualization of Archeological Sites.
- http://www.rovina-project.eu/
- Traversability analysis based on depth images from Kinectlike sensor.
- Funded by European Commission.
- The paper on the project is submitted to ECMR 2013 (European Conference on Mobile Robotics)

## **Trainings and Courses**

#### **CITEC Robotics Summer School**

- Various presentations on robotics topic
- 5-day workshop on multi-sensoric data aquisition, focus on Kinect and eye-tracking cameras.
- https://www.cit-ec.de/

#### AI Course (Online)

A course by Sebastian Thrun and Peter Norvig on AI.

#### AI for Robotics (Online)

o A course by Sebastian Thrun on Udacity.

#### **CUDA Programming (Online)**

Yet not finished course on Udacity.

## Languages

- English (IELTS 8.0)
- o German (B2)
- Russian (Native)
- Ukrainian (Native)

## **Skills**

#### Platforms and libraries

- WindowsOpenCVAndroidOpenNIPCL
- ROSOpenGL

#### **Programming and markup languages**

- ∘ C++ ∘ Matlab/Octave ∘ CMake
- JavaPythonXmlSQLite

#### Fields of interest

- Mobile Robotics
- Image Processing
- o Pattern Recognition
- Machine Learning
- Kinect
- Computer Vision
- Autonomous Navigation
- SLAM

## **Hobbies**

- Android-programmingPhotographyVolleyball

- Playing guitar Rock music
- Skiing
- Biking
- New technologyLearning new stuff

## References

References upon request.